CHRISTOPHER POIRIER

UX DESIGNER VANCOUVER, BC



CONTACT

204-406-5358

hello@cpeartree.com

www www.cpeartree.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/cpeartree

A New Media Design and Web Development student in pursuit of a challenging and rewarding UI/UX internship, utilizing my experience and education in user research, design, and testing to create intuitive and user-centred digital products that drive business success.

EDUCATION

New Media Design and Web DevelopmentBritish Columbia Institute of Technology
2021-2023

SOFTWARE & SKILLS

Figma Graphic Design

XD Digital Storytelling

Photoshop Project Management

Illustrator Account Management

InDesign Research

Final Cut Pro Leadership

HTML Sales

CSS

PORTFOLIO

www.cpeartree.com



HIGHLIGHTED PROJECT

UI/UX / APP DEVELOPMENT

Cato Weather | 2022

 School project focused on the development of a children's educational weather application. The project included creating a concept, researching market comparison, assessing market viability and designing wireframes.

EXPERIENCE

SALES & SERVICE

DU/ER | 2019-2020

- Responsible for driving standard operating procedures, inventory management, and sales coaching/feedback.
- Growth of wholesale business & trade show presence
- Successfully assisted in the operations of the transition to a large-scale warehouse

APPLE SOLUTIONS CONSULTANT

Apple | 2012 - 2018

- Drove Apple's channel partner sales strategy in the Winnipeg and Vancouver markets.
- Engaged and supported store leadership teams on market strategy, while providing education and consultation to align sales teams with Apple's brand solutions.